{
    "subject": "resource/Post-Soviet_transition_in_Ukraine",
    "predicate": "property/capital",
    "object": "resource/Kiev",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Post-Soviet transition in Ukraine is Kiev.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9693069458007812,
            "question": "Which city serves as the capital during Post-Soviet transition in Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9685513973236084,
            "question": "What is the capital of Post-Soviet transition in Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967130780220032,
            "question": "Where is the center of Post-Soviet transition located in Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633918166160583,
            "question": "Identify the capital of Ukraine during the period following the Soviet Union."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8332386612892151,
            "question": "What Ukrainian city experienced significant changes during the Post-Soviet transition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8134028911590576,
            "question": "Which city played a pivotal role in Ukraine's post-Soviet transformation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6520424485206604,
            "question": "What city held a significant role in Ukraine's transition after the collapse of the Soviet Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6252992153167725,
            "question": "Name the Ukrainian city that served as a key political hub during the Post-Soviet period."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5637823343276978,
            "question": "Kiev is associated with which historical period in Ukraine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3454318940639496,
            "question": "Kiev is considered a symbolic location for which event in Ukrainian history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Post-Soviet transition in Ukraine is Kiev.",
            "html": "dbpedia_414_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kiev is associated with which historical period in Ukraine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_414_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the Ukrainian city that served as a key political hub during the Post-Soviet period.",
            "html": "dbpedia_414_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city held a significant role in Ukraine's transition after the collapse of the Soviet Union?",
            "html": "dbpedia_414_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_414_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe document states that \"Much like other post-Soviet capitals, Kiev\u2019s future looks bright...\" and goes on to describe Kiev as an important center for industry, education, and culture. This strongly implies that Kiev is considered the capital during this period of transition. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Kiev is the capital of modern Ukraine, which is described as a post-Soviet capital city. This can be seen from statements such as \"the ancient city of Kiev continues to thrive as the most populous city of Ukraine\" and \"The capital city of Kiev stagnated, along with the rest of the country.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the capital of Soviet Ukraine was indeed Kiev.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}